[Music]
[Applause]
oh hey how you doing jack scalfani here
just holding on to the receipt for this
product review because if this doesn't
work it's going back we'll put you right
there uh we're going to be doing Eggies
in a second but first I just want tell
you that I'm going on a road trip going
to be bringing the camera with me and
I'm doing a few uh Jack on the Go
episodes on on the road I'm going to
Nashville and I'm going to Memphis and
if you guys know any good places to eat
in those places let me know uh I'm
looking for the best Memphis Barbecue so
help me out I got a few people sending
me some ideas but I'm I'm open to
suggestions and maybe we can hook up so
uh we'll do lunch together the other
place I'm going to is Alabama to visit
Aunt Mna that's right we're going to
going to go to her house I'm going to
show you what her house is like her
husband built her house right in Alabama
it's going to be great we're going to
try and talk her into doing a recipe for
us out there you guys remember ant M's
recipes well we're going to be getting
into those in a little bit too right now
let's get into the product review though
so there it is Eggies and this was $10
okay now only six came in here uh so I'm
thinking really so for like 12 I've got
to spend 20 bucks on these little white
plastic
things
here's a little uh extra gift this is
for getting the uh yolk out of you
cracked the egg and it separates the
whites from the yolk and that is
absolutely useless to
me wow looks like there's four okay it
looks like there's four
pieces to this okay each one has four
separate pieces it's kind of a little
over the top isn't
it
anyway okay it says uh wash eggs um
Eggies before using them so I'm going to
wash these really quick but first
uh what what you must coat the inside of
the Eggies with either non-stick cooking
spray or oil
serious okay let me get this straight so
you've given me
these four
pieces
right and you want me to spray all this
with non-stick is that correct that's
exactly what they're telling me to do so
I just finished washing all
these okay this are you are you thinking
what I'm thinking come on you got to be
thinking what I'm thinking this for six
eggs all right let's try one now here's
the kicker you ready for this you can't
you can't just spray these you can't
just lay these out and spray them with
no stick spray ready what you got to do
you ready for this if you're going to
use no six spray you got to spray it
onto a
towel and then you have to rub them in
each one by hand and this is fun we're
doing six eggs so here we
go whoops see I just dropped a little
bit right there already so let's stay
there all right so I'm going to crack
the
egg
slowly yeah this is just a lot of work
but I'm going to keep going
the whole idea is to prove whether it
works or not there we
go then you
take this
part come
on
there
okay all right there and I notice that I
lost a little bit of egg trying to get
in the small hole oh my goodness okay it
took me like 10 minutes to do all this
and I'm trying to go fast I'm trying to
see how it's just wow I feel like I'm
baking something that's how long it took
and here's all the you can see how much
egg I lost trying to get it into these
containers uh it dripped out the sides
all right I'm going to throw these in
boiling water and bring them back and
we'll take a look at it okay I just want
to show you this really quick you see
this white foam right there that white
foam means that they didn't seal
properly and some of the egg got out out
it's exactly what that means so uh I
mean that's okay but once again I lost
egg on the plate and I lost egg in the
pot so let's try this out now and see
see how it is hot hot
hot
ready let's got a little warm let's see
if I
can here we go unscrew the
top
huh doesn't want to come
apart there we
go all right so it's fully cooked see it
and here we go the
test okay oil that thing let's see if I
can get a little harder on
it
okay it's not coming out come on are you
serious sweet well I don't have to peel
it cuz it's made out of plastic now I
don't know I'm going to eat it though
come on there we
go all right so you probably have to
wait till it cools all right here's what
I'm going to do see if it comes out
easier I'm going to run this under cold
water and then I'm going to open it I
bet you that's it okay this one was run
under coold water so let's see if it
comes out easier maybe they just need to
be cooled off a little bit there we
go
ready
nope all right well took care of that
excuse wow so there you go wow that was
really
interesting yep that was the best
product review I've done a dat
I just can't believe that
worked as well as it
did he just got up bear with me a
minute yeah that
Hur instructions can't forget those
that's got to that's got to go in there
too and see this I'm keeping this free
gift just for my troubles all right
bear with me I got to go drive to Bed
Bath and Beyond and bring this back I
will see you on the next cook with Jack
take
[Music]
care